[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Scorpions are known to glow when exposed to this type of light.", "correct_answer": "Blacklight", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Infrared light", "Laser light"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Forrest Gump, Mrs. Gump (played by Sally Field) ran a boarding house where a young Forrest taught one of the special guests how to dance. Who was this special guest?", "correct_answer": "Elvis Presley", "incorrect_answers": ["Fred Astaire", "Dick Van Dyke", "Gene Kelly"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many people die of air pollution around the world each year?", "correct_answer": "3 million", "incorrect_answers": ["500,000", "50,000", "1 million"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the Wayans brothers starred in the 1996 movie The Glimmer Man?", "correct_answer": "Keenen", "incorrect_answers": ["Damon", "Marlon", "Dwayne"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This former presidents name was a little bit too close to raygun to start the Star Wars Missle Defense System. Who was this former action hero?", "correct_answer": "Ronald Reagan", "incorrect_answers": ["George W. Bush", "George Bush", "Bill Clinton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these countries does not border Georgia?", "correct_answer": "Belarus", "incorrect_answers": ["Armenia", "Azerbaijain", "Turkey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor portrayed the popular superhero Superman in the superexpensive 2006 movie Superman Returns?", "correct_answer": "Brandon Routh", "incorrect_answers": ["Tobey Maguire", "Matt Damon", "Christian Slater"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who are the presidents on Mount Rushmore?", "correct_answer": "Washington, Jefferson, T. Roosevelt, Lincoln", "incorrect_answers": ["Adams, Washington, Johnson, F. Roosevelt", "Washington, Adams, Lincoln, Hamilton", "Lincoln, Kennedy, Regan, Washington"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the popular Chinese Peking Duck traditionally served with?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Spring onions", "Sweet noodle sauce", "Pancakes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In calculus we never use complex (or imaginary) numbers.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which tiny lake located in Tibet is the highest lake on Earth?", "correct_answer": "Lhagba Pool", "incorrect_answers": ["Rush Lake", "Laguna Lobato", "Poquentica Lake"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the popular solitaire game, in which you alternate suits building down, and build up in the same suit on the aces?", "correct_answer": "Klondike", "incorrect_answers": ["Fish", "Casino", "Spider"]}]